{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "55 + 25",
      "answer": 80
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 99",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 72",
      "answer": 162
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 50",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 89",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 61",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 21",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 63",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 90",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 56",
      "answer": 154
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 39",
      "answer": 46
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 49",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 54",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 48",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 92",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 78",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 48",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 21",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "66 + 65",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 70",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 39",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 68",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 49",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 97",
      "answer": 154
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 30",
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 90",
      "answer": 154
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 60",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 21",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 7",
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 41",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 17",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 34",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 100",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 16",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 2",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 64",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 86",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 1",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 85",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 15",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 14",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 33",
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 73",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 28",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 63",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 78",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 87",
      "answer": 144
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 95",
      "answer": 171
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 52",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 95",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 32",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 69",
      "answer": 162
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 30",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 34",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 68",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 62",
      "answer": 65
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 2",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 22",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 70",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 14",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 92",
      "answer": 172
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 55",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 95",
      "answer": 195
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 31",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 80",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 47",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 15",
      "answer": 46
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 74",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 43",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 43",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 75",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 59",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 37",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 25",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 85",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 15",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 51",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 21",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 60",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 63",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 33",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 11",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 1",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 98",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 85",
      "answer": 179
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 26",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 88",
      "answer": 183
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 94",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 45",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 63",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 78",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 30",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 12",
      "answer": 66
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 38",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 89",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 31",
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 11",
      "answer": 51
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 37",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 44",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 16",
      "answer": 20
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 5,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 400,
      "to": 500
    }
  }
}